ELISABET VAZQUEZ

Los Angeles, CA | (+1) 310-254-0759 | elisabetvz.com | elisabetv.design@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/elisabetv | Creative Direction + Design Services | Available for Freelance Projects | Open to Full-Time or Contractor Position

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm an interdisciplinary creative focusing on Graphic Design, specializing in typography, brand design, layout design and art direction. I acquired a Political Science degree from UCL exploring a range of subjects, mainly focused on international relations, economics, social psychology, cognitive approaches to foreign policy, and strategic project management. My diverse background has allowed me to hone my problem-solving skills to provide effective solutions and innovative design.

EDUCATION

UCL (UNIVERSITY COLLEGE LONDON)

LONDON, UK

Bachelor of Arts - Politics, Sociology and East European Studies.

SEP. 2019 - JUN. 2022

- Grade: 2:1 (i.e.: 3.7 GPA)
- Dissertation on Cognitive Approaches to Foreign Policy Analysis

UCLA EXTENSION LOS ANGELES, USA

Certificate, Design Communication Arts Certificate, Directing

Jun. 2021 - Aug. 2022

Mar. 2022 - Aug. 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

MINA BAIE (Retail Company)

LOS ANGELES, USA SEP. 2022-current

Junior Graphic Designer

• Designed Emails, GIFs for Reels, Stories and Posts. Retouched + Color Corrected Images for Web + Socials.

JUICE HOUSE (Creative Agency)

REMOTE

Creative Intern

SEP. 2022-current

- Creative Direction, Social Planning and Management of @juicehousecreative account
- Content Creation and Ideation for Artist's Personal Brand + Socials, working with @itsduncanlaurence, @sofiavaldes, @trinsgby,

MOSAIC (NGO) LOS ANGELES, USA

Creative Team Lead

JUN. 2022-current

 Led a team of 6, art directing and creating graphics and social media content, as well as supervising a team for motion graphics, digital design, photography. Main focus: graphics, photography, social media management.

Hillsong UK (NGO)

LONDON, UK

Photographer

SEP. 2019 - MAR. 2022

Providing Photography and Photo Editing for weekly events and conferences.

A21 UK (NGO, Human Trafficking Relief)

LONDON, UK

Social Media Manager

MAR. 2020-AUG. 2020

- Led a Creative Team of 5, to create graphics and copywriting for social media campaigns.
- Developed brand awareness in social channels through content management, strategy, planning and goal setting.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

TBN España (Studio, Film & TV)

MADRID, SPAIN

Jan. 2018-Aug. 2018

English-Spanish Translation and Subtitling of TV Episodes.

LANGUAGES

English (fluent, C2); Spanish (native); French (advanced, C1).

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Photoshop | Illustrator | InDesign | CSS | HTML | After Effects | MS Office | Power Point | Research | Scheduling | Photography | Lightroom | Sketch | Social Media Management | Project Management

OTHER INFORMATION & CERTIFICATES

- Confident Copywriting 6-week Short Course from UAL College of Communication (2020).
- Coded and designed my own portfolio website (elisabetvz.com) using HTML and CSS.
- 1-year Leadership Program covering subjects as critical thinking, theology, personal development (2020–2021)